It's a thin line between love and friendship.
Something Borrowed is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Luke Greenfield.
Though Rachel is a successful attorney and a loyal,
generous friend, she is still single.
After one drink too many at her 30th-birthday celebration, Rachel unexpectedly falls into bed with
her longtime crush, Dex -- who happens to be engaged to her best friend, Darcy.
Ramifications of the liaison threaten to destroy the women's lifelong friendship, while
Ethan, Rachel's confidant, harbors a potentially explosive secret of his own.
Rachel, played by Ginnifer Goodwin.
Darcy, played by Kate Hudson.
Dex, played by Colin Egglesfield.
Ethan, played by John Krasinski.
Marcus, played by Steve Howey.
Claire, played by Ashley Williams.
Something Borrowed is a 2011 American romantic comedy film based on Emily Giffin's 2005 book of the same name, directed by Luke
Greenfield, starring Ginnifer Goodwin, Kate Hudson, Colin Egglesfield, and John Krasinski and distributed by Warner Bros.
Released on May 6, 2011, the film received negative
reviews from critics and grossed $60 million.
The film explores themes of new york city, based on novel or
book, cheating, pregnancy, birthday party.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.